Contact

rosaomtz@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rosa-o-flores-09564313 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing

Critical Care

Registered Nurses

Languages

English (Full Professional)

Spanish (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Registered Nurse

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Pediatric Advanced Life Support Basic Life Support

Rosa O. Flores

Clinical Nurse Manager ICU/NTICU at HCA Healthcare Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Experienced Intensive Care Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Precepting, Patient Advocacy, Nursing Education, Neuro, Trauma and Medical-Surgical. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor's Degree in Nursing.

Experience

HCA Healthcare

6 years 11 months

Critical Care Registered Nurse May 2014 - Present (6 years 1 month)

HCA Houston Healthcare Clearlake

Relief Nurse Leader: Present

Unit Based Council Committee Chair: Present

Professional Practice Council: January 2019-Present

Unit Based Council Committee Co-Chair: January 2017 - Present

Peer Interviewing Panel: April 2016 - Present

Buddy Program: June 2015 - Present

Preceptor: May 2015 - Present

Education Committee: June 2018- Present Shared Governance: January 2019-Present Annual Competency Educator 2018-Present

HCA Certified Preceptor: 2017-Present

Employee of the Month: February 2018 Employee of the Month: October 2015 Employee of the Month: January 2015

Patient Experience Rewards & Recognition Luncheon Invitee: March 2016
Patient Experience Rewards & Recognition Luncheon Invitee: November 2015

Intensive Care Unit RN July 2013 - May 2014 (11 months)

Education

Grand Canyon University

Master's degree, Nursing Education · (2018 - 2020)

Grand Canyon University

Bachelor's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2014 - 2015)

Lone Star College
Associate's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2009 - 2012)